<cmm spl="F9111" oidate="20061212" tsn="1" docnbr="0000" lang="EN"
chapnbr="31" sectnbr="64" subjnbr="06" type="cmm" prelim="0" chg="N"
revdate="20061212">
<title>COMPONENT MAINTENANCE MANUAL WITH ILLUSTRATED PARTS LIST</title>
<partinfo model="AIRBUS">
<cmpnom>BACK LIGHTING MODULE (BLM) </cmpnom>
<mfrpnr>
<pnr>E24906AA</pnr>
<mfr>F9111</mfr>
</mfrpnr>
</partinfo>
<mfmatr><trlist chg="N" key="TRLIST" revdate="20070921">
<title>Record of temporary revisions</title>
<isempty/></trlist><sblist chg="N" key="SBLIST" revdate="20070921"><?Pub Dtl?>
<title>SERVICE BULLETIN LIST</title>
<para>The SB List reflects the incorporation status of Service Bulletins
edited by: THALES Avionics S.A. (Vendor Code F9111).</para>
<para>The SB List has the following five columns to indicate SBs and
their status:</para>
<para>SB number (SB No.) This is the number of the SB. If no SB affects
the manual content, the comment None is given.</para>
<para>SB Revision (SB Rev) This is the revision number of the SB.</para>
<para>SB Subject This is the subject of the SB.</para>
<para>Modification state (modification state) This is the equipment
part number  modification state of the unit.</para>
<para>Incorporation date (INSERTED Date) SB status or incorporation
date is indicated in this column as follow: If the SB is fully incorporated
into the manual, the incorporation date is indicated. If the SB is
partially incorporated into the manual, the field is left blank. If
the SB data does not affect the manual content, the comment NO EFFECT
is given.</para>
<para>Incorporation date (INSERTED No.) This is the revision number
of the updating Component Maintenance Manual (CMM).</para>
<note><para>The Service Information Letters (SIL) which affect the
manual content are listed at the end of the table.</para></note>
<para></para>
<sbdata><sbnbr></sbnbr>
<sbtitle></sbtitle>
<issdate></issdate>
</sbdata></sblist></mfmatr>
<pgblk chapnbr="31" sectnbr="64" subjnbr="06" pgblknbr="0" confnbr="1"
chg="N" key="PGBLK-31-64-06-0-1" revdate="20070921">
<title>INTRODUCTION</title>
<task chapnbr="31" sectnbr="64" subjnbr="06" func="871" seq="801"
confltr="A" varnbr="01" pgblknbr="0" confnbr="1" chg="N"
key="TASK-31-64-06-871-801-A01" revdate="20070921">
<title>General</title>
<topic>
<title>Purpose of the Manual</title>
<prclist1>
<prcitem1>
<prcitem>
<unlist bulltype="NONE">
<unlitem><para>The Component Maintenance Manual (CMM) conforms to
ATA Specification No. 2200.</para></unlitem>
<unlitem><para>The CMM provides shop verified procedures that enable
a mechanic to restore the component to its serviceable condition in
the overhaul shop.</para></unlitem>
<unlitem><para>The Abbreviated Component Maintenance Manual (ACMM)
is a brief version of the CMM, for simple components which require
periodic maintenance and/or testing.</para></unlitem>
<unlitem><para>The ACMM/CMM is prepared by the Manufacturer for each
Repairable or Overhaulable unit.</para></unlitem>
<unlitem><para>THALES Avionics Technical Publications use both metric
and non-metric system of measurement. The system used in the original
reference documents is given first, followed by the conversion into
the other system in brackets.</para></unlitem>
</unlist>
</prcitem>
</prcitem1>
</prclist1>
</topic>
</task>
</pgblk>
<ipl chapnbr="31" sectnbr="64" subjnbr="06" pgblknbr="0" chg="N"
key="IPL" revdate="20090923">
<isempty/></ipl>
</cmm><?Pub Caret?>
<?Pub *0000003601 0?>
